慢着  慢着
Wait a minute, wait.
你是说这个女演员
You're telling me this actress person...
是唯一一个对你的示爱毫无回应的女人吗
...is the only woman you ever wanted who didn't want you back?
是啊  天哪
Yeah. Oh, my God.
你的人生就是这样吗
Is this what it's like to be you?
-你真的很喜欢她啊  -你都想象不出
- You're crazy about her, huh? - You have no idea.
我们在台上时  我可以吻她摸她
When we're on stage, I get to kiss her and touch her.
结果她却跟导演回家
She goes home with the director...
我就心如刀割
...and it's like somebody's ripping out my heart.
看你这样感觉真好
Oh, it's so great to see you feeling like this.
莫妮卡  爸早上打电话来
Monica. Dad called this morning.
施薇亚姑姑过世了
Aunt Sylvia passed away.
好耶  太好了
Yes!! Yes! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
我们都很震惊
We were all pretty shaken up about it.
我漏听了什么
Am I missing something?
在某种程度上  死亡不是悲伤的事吗
I thought death was supposed to be sad, in a way.
施薇亚姑姑...
Well, Aunt Sylvia was...
不是一个好人
... not a nice person.
她是个残忍的糟老太婆
She was a cruel, cranky old bitch.
我很难过她死了
And I'm sorry she died.
爸爸有没有说娃娃屋归我
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
-娃娃屋归你了  -我得到娃娃屋了
- You get the dollhouse. - I get the dollhouse!
娃娃住的屋子  好酷哦
A house for dolls! That is so cool.
我小时候只有铁桶
When I was a kid, I had a barrel.
菲比  你拿铁桶当娃娃屋吗
Uh, Pheebs, you had a barrel for a dollhouse?
不  就是一个铁桶
No, just a barrel.
你可以玩我的娃娃屋
You know what? You can play with my dollhouse.
真的吗  真的吗
Really?! Really?!
随时欢迎
Any time you want.
我小时候总是渴望玩这个娃娃屋
When I was young I wanted to play with this dollhouse.
但是不行  只准看不准玩
But no! It was to be looked at,never played with.
我奶奶以前也是这样告诫我的
My Grandmother used to say that exact same thing to me.
-苏菲好啊  -你好  瑞秋
- Hey, Sophie!  - Hey, Rach!
谢谢你请我吃饭  钱德勒
Thanks for lunch. Chandler.
你不必这么麻烦  一路送我回来的
You didn't have to walk me all the way back up here.
没事  不客气
That's okay. No problem.
宝贝  你知道我们不会把女性内衣放在办公室吧
Honey um, honey, you do realize that we don't keep the women's lingerie here in the office?
我当然知道
Yes, I realize that.
-夏季型录  -就是这个
- Summer catalog. - That's the stuff.
瑞秋  给我范思哲的发货清单
Rachel, I need the Versace invoice.
你不是我的员工
You don't work for me.
乔安娜  我的朋友钱德勒·宾
Joanna, this is my friend Chandler Bing.
这是乔安娜
Joanna.
宾  很棒的姓
Bing? That's a great name.
那是盖尔语的"火鸡煮好了"
It's Gaelic for,"Thy turkey's done."
-我走了  幸会  -幸会
-I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you. -You too.
拜拜  钱德勒
Bye, Chandler.
他怎么样
So what's wrong with him?
没什么  他都这样疯疯癫癫的
Nothing. He's just goofy like that.
我都没感觉了
I actually hardly notice it anymore.
我是说他已婚吗  有对象吗
I mean, is he married or involved with anyone?
不  他未婚  没有对象
No, no. He's not married or involved with anyone.
瑞秋  这样吧  我看还是算了
Rachel, actually, you know what? Forget it.
-需要的话  我可以帮你探探口风  -真的吗
- I'll ask him for you, if you want. - Would you?
这样会不会太可悲  太饥渴
Or is it too sad and desperate,
你懂的  就像苏菲一样
you know, something Sophie would do?
-我能听见  -我知道
- I am here. - I know that.
你们看
Look at it!
壁纸有点褪色  没关系
Wallpaper's a little faded. That's okay.
地毯有点翘起来
Carpet's a little loose.
硬木地板
Hardwood floors?!
-莫妮卡  它真美啊  -可不是
- Monica, it's so beautiful! - I know!
我来了  准备开玩
So I'm here, ready to play!
我带了一堆东西放在屋子里  快看
I brought a bunch of stuff for the house, so check it out.
这是什么
What's this?
狗狗  每栋房子都应该有只狗
That's a dog. Every house should have a dog.
不能大到可以在屋顶上撒尿
Not one that can pee on the roof.
它这么大也许是
Maybe it's so big because
因为房子盖在辐射废料掩埋地上
the house was built on radioactive waste.
这是防止房子打喷嚏用的吗
And is this in case the house sneezes?
不是  那是阁楼里的鬼
No, that's the ghost for the attic.
-我不要鬼  -谁都不想闹鬼
- I don't want a ghost. - Well, nobody wants a ghost.
但是这里闹鬼
But you've got one...
因为房子盖在印地安古坟场上
... because the house is sitting on an ancient lndian burial ground.
慢着  这栋房子盖在辐射废料掩埋地
Wait a minute. The house was built on radioactive waste...
和印地安古坟场上
...and an ancient lndian burial ground?
那是不可能的
That would never happen.
显然你太不了解美国政府了
Obviously you don't know much about the U.S. government.
-我有事找你  -好  什么事
- I need to talk to you. - Sure. What's up?
抱歉  我是说钱德勒
Oh, sorry. I meant Chandler.
我知道
I know.
有事记得找我
Well, if something comes up....
恭喜你们度过尴尬期
I'm glad you guys are past that little awkward phase.
我的上司乔安娜  你一离开
My boss. Joanna. When you left...
她就问起你的事...
...she started asking questions about you....
看上眼了是吧
Liked what she saw?
喜欢我的表现  对吧
Dug my action, did she?
在探听小钱钱的事了吧
Checking out the Chan Chan Man!
听起来...
That was...
怪怪的
...surreal.
怎样  有兴趣吗
What do you think? Are you interested?
她还不错  蛮漂亮的  好吧
She seemed cool. Attractive. I'll do it.
谢谢你  钱德勒  太好了  她会爱死我
Thank you, Chandler. This is great. She's gonna love me.
恐龙出击  大家快躲进屋里
Dinosaur attack! Quick, everybody into the house!
你知道吗  菲比  到此为止
All right, Phoebe, you know what? That's it. That's it.
我不要恐龙  鬼和超级大狗  好吗
No dinosaurs, no ghosts, no giant dogs, okay?
他们比例不对  也不是维多利亚风格
They're not the right size, they're not Victorian
总之一点也不相衬
and they just don't go.
好
Fine.
恐龙  我们走
Come, dinosaur.
没有想像力的房子不欢迎我们
We're not welcome in the house of no imagination.
菲比  趁我们还在讨论这个话题
Pheebs, while we're hovering around the subject.
我想告诉你  恐龙不会汪汪叫
I have to say that dinosaurs... ...they don't go, "ruff!"
小恐龙会
The little ones do.
-嗨  凯特  -早
-Hey, Kate. -Morning.
我去了你上周说的那家餐厅...
I went to that restaurant you talked about last week...
美女
Hey, lovely.
过来  跟我聊一下
Come, talk to me for a minute.
我在那里吃饭  很好吃  我点了鱼
I ate the food. It was good. I had the fish.
我是萝伦  凯特的替角
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani.
我知道
I know.
我是你的超级影迷
I'm a big fan of yours.
什么
What?
我以前经常翘课  好回家看《我们的岁月》中的
I used to schedule my classes so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
拉莫瑞医生
...on Days of our Lives.
-别乱讲  真的吗  -当然
- Get out of here. Really - Absolutely.
结果他们让你掉到电梯井里
But then they dropped you down that elevator shaft.
他们是把我踢掉了
They gave me the shaft, all right.
你好幽默
You're so funny.
你排完戏要做什么
Listen, what are you doing after rehearsal?
要不要去喝一杯
You want to get a drink or something?
好啊  听起来不错
Yeah, sure. A drink sounds great.
-帅  呆会见  -好
- Cool. I'll see you then. - All right.
好了  该演戏了  会说话的道具们
All right. It's time to act, my talking props.
你们看  我的新娃娃屋
Look everybody! Look at my new dollhouse!
你们看
Look, look!
这是什么
Hey, what's this?
我用溜滑梯取代楼梯  看
It's a slide instead of stairs. Look.
很有意思嘛  菲比
Very interesting, Phoebe.
这是什么
What's this?
甘草房  所有家具都可以吃
The licorice room. You can eat all the furniture.
客人来了  可以睡在滑轮床上
And when guests come over, they can stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
这栋房子有够酷的
This is the coolest house ever!
有人要跟我进芳香室吗
Does anyone want to join me in the Aroma Room?
-漂亮  -我要
- All right. - I would.
各位  各位
Hey, guys? Guys!
你们看到我的新瓷器柜了吗
Did you see my new china cabinet?
看喔  看喔
Watch. Watch.
还有喔
And? And?
我爸的房子也会那样
Hey, my father's house does that.
怎么样  快都告诉我
How did it go? Tell me everything!
电影很好看  晚餐很好吃
The movie was great...dinner was great,
凉爽的纽约夜晚最宜人不过
and there's nothing like a cool, crisp New York evening.
当然啦  我一点也不尽兴
Of course, I didn't get to enjoy any of that
因为乔安娜真的好无聊
because Joanna's such a big dull dud!
钱德勒太棒了
Chandler is fantastic!
-什么  -你知道一拍即合吧
- What? - You know how people just click?
他来接我  我打开门
He came by to pick me up, I opened the door
感觉一拍即合
and it was just like,"click!"
-他有告诉你吗  -我...
- Did he tell you? - Oh I...
他的心肠很好  他是不是有副好心肠啊
Oh, and he's got such a good heart! Doesn't he have a good heart?
而且他好体贴
And he's so sweet.
他说他会打来  要立刻转给我
He said he'd call, so put him straight through.
-太好了  -不要扫兴
- lsn't this great? - Don't spoil it.
别这样  宝贝  不要走  求你了
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
好吗
What do you say?
你好
Hello.
是你啊  等一下
It's you. Just one sec.
我要接个电话
I'm going to take this call.
等我回来  希望台上会出现...
When I continue, I hope there will appear on-stage...
一种神奇的东西  在戏剧界称之为...
...this magical thing that in the theater we call...
"入戏"
...committing to the moment!
他跟卡通人物一样白痴
The guy's like a cartoon.
你到底看上他哪一点
What do you see in him, anyway?
他刚好很聪明
He happens to be brilliant.
比你那位毛衣女郎好多了
Which is more than I can say for that sweater you're dating.
我不是看上她的毛衣
I'm not interested in her sweater.
毛衣底下才重要
It's what's underneath her sweater that counts.
而且...
And besides...
你几时开始关心我跟谁交往
...since when do you care who I'm with?
我才不关心  怎么  你希望我关心吗
I don't care. Why, do you want me to care?
你希望我希望你关心吗
Do you want me to want you to care?
你呢
Do you?
什么
What?
我实在很不想说  不过我们继续排吧
Okay. I'm afraid to say this, but let's pick up where we left off.
别这样  宝贝  不要走  求你了
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
好吗
What do you say?
我没有理由留下来
I've got no reason to stay.
停
Stop!
停  别再演了
Stop it! You must stop!
你们是烂演员
You are bad actors!
这是出烂戏
This is a terrible play!
明天早上见
I'll see you in the morning.
真不敢相信一星期后就要上台了
I can't believe we go on in a week.
没问题的
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
既然提早收工  你想去画马克杯吗
Since we're getting off early, do you want to go paint mugs?
什么
What?
就是我昨晚说的那个地方啊
You know at the place I told you about last night?
对了  那里可以画马克杯
Yeah, with the mug-painting.
我听得很用心
I was so listening to that.
但是你知道吗  我今晚想好好练戏
But you know what? I need to kind of work on my stuff tonight.
好吧  那明天见
Ok, I'll see you tomorrow.
-好啦  -晚安
-Okay. - Good night!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好吧
Yeah, I guess.
这场戏怎么办
What are we gonna do about the scene?
不知道
I don't know.
也许应该再激烈一点
Maybe if it had more heat.
什么意思
Well, how do you mean?
爱德莉安在寻找留下来的理由  对吧
Adrianne's looking for a reason to stay, right?
维克多不能只是亲她  他必须...
Victor can't just kiss her. He's gotta...
必须给她有力的理由
... he's gotta give her a reason.
也许他可以跟她舌吻
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
或者...
Or maybe...
他可以捉住她  把她抱起来
... maybe he could grab her and lift her up.
然后爱德莉安用腿圈住他的腰
Then Adrianne could wrap her legs around his waist.
扯开他的衣服
Then she could rip off his shirt
亲吻他的胸部  肚子
and kiss his chest and stomach.
他可以用牙齿脱掉她的衣服
Then he could use his teeth, his teenth to undo her dress and...
然后咬她
and bite her!
在结尾的部份  他可以占有她
Then right when the scene ends, he could take her...
用他那原始的  兽性的...
...with this raw, animal....
像这样吗
Something like that?
跟我想的差不多
That's pretty much what I had in mind.
现在喝酒太早了吧
It's a little early to be drinking.
我没醉  我跟凯特终于有进展了
No, no, things finally happened with Kate.
真的吗  太好了
You're kidding? That's great.
感觉好棒
It was so amazing.
做完爱之后...
After the lovemaking...
天啊
Oh, my.
我看着她睡觉看了好久
... I just watched her sleep for hours.
就这样吸气...
Just breathing in...
吐气
...and breathing out.
我知道她在做梦  因为...
I knew she was dreaming because...
她的眼睛一直这样
... her eyes kept going like this.
我跟你说  乔安娜完全误会了  好吗
I'm telling you, Joanna's got it all wrong, okay?
我只是说今晚很愉快  改天再聚
All I said was, "This was fun. Let's do it again sometime.
我再打给你
I'll give you a call."
我还想她为什么觉得你会打给她
I wonder why she thinks you're going to call her?
约完会都要这么说
It's what you say at the end of a date.
你就不能说  很高兴认识你  晚安
You can't just say,"Nice to meet you. Good night?"
当着她的面吗
To her face?
约会结束了  我站在那儿
lt's the end of the date. I'm standing there...
我知道她在等我这句话
...she's waiting for me to say I'll call her...
所以我就说了  就这么脱口而出
...and it comes out. I can't help it.
我也没办法
It's a compulsion.
别这么较真  瑞秋
Come on, Rach,
男人说要联络  也不见得会联络
When a guy says he'll call, it doesn't mean he's going to call.
你没碰到过
This never happened to you?
他们都会打给我
Well, they always called.
杀了我吧
Bite me.
-他打来没有  -没有  对不起
- Did he call? - No, sorry.
为什么  他说要打来怎么还不打来
Why? He said he'd call. Why hasn't he called?
也许他被你这个美丽成功的女强人吓到了
Maybe he's intimidated by smart, strong, successful women.
苏菲  不要拍我的马屁了
Sophie, will you please climb out of my butt.
他为什么还不打来  瑞秋  为什么
Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why?
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
也许他会尴尬  因为你是我的上司
Maybe he feels awkward because you're my boss.
尴尬  他为什么要尴尬
Awkward? Why should he feel awkward?
要说尴尬也该是你尴尬
The only person that should feel awkward is you,
你没叫他不要打给我吧
and you didn't tell him not to call me, did you?
因为要是你不喜欢你朋友跟你上司约会
If you're uncomfortable with your friend dating someone you work for...
我们可以想办法解决
...there are always ways to fix that.
打给她  现在就打给她
Call her. Call her now!
我满手都被纸割伤了
Multiple so many paper cuts.
"他为什么还不打来  瑞秋
"Why hasn't he called, Rachel?
"为什么  为什么  我不懂"
"Why,why? I don't understand!"
为什么  他明明说会打给我  这是为什么呢
Why? He said he would call. Why? Why?
钱德勒  我跟你说她失控了  她疯了
Chandler, I'm telling you, she's flipped out! She's gone crazy!
那把电话拿来吧
Well, give me the phone then.
求你了  这不是闹着玩的
Come on, this isn't funny.
她觉得你不联络是我的错
She thinks it's my fault that you haven't called her.
你一定要打给她
You have to call her.
总不能过了这么久才打去说
You can't call somebody after this long to say:
"我提醒你一下  我不喜欢你"
"In case you didn't notice, I don't like you."
那就再带她出去一次
Then you'll have to take her out again.
不要  她很无聊  而且在眼角
No. She's really dull, and she gets this...
有一大块恶心的睫毛膏印子
...gross mascara-goop thing in the corner of her eye!
我不管  不管
I don't care! I don't care!
你再约她一次  把话说清楚
You'll take her out again and end it...
让她知道自己没希望
...in a way she knows it's atually ended.
不管有多困难  千万别说你会再联络
I don't care how hard it is. Don't tell her you'll call her again!
好  随你
All right, fine!
但只能吃午餐  不能超过一小时
But just an lunch date, no more than an hour.
从今以后  我自己泡马子
From now on, I get my own dates.
你不要再帮我牵线了
I don't want you setting me up with anybody ever again!
没问题
That's fine!
-我只是说说  -我知道
- That's just a lot of big talk. - I know.
-莫妮卡  -我在洗澡
- Moni. - I'm in the shower!
失火了  失火了
Fire! There's a fire! Fire!
我跟萝伦谈过了  跟她说了我们的事
I talked to Lauren. I told her how things were with us.
你跟马歇尔说了吗
Did you talk to Marshall?
说什么
About what?
我们之间的事啊
About what happened with us.
没有  他没有必要知道
No, there's really no reason why he should find out.
我们就别小题大作了  好吗
So let's not make a big deal out of it, okay?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我没有小题大作
It was a big deal.
别说昨晚对你毫无意义
You can't tell me last night didn't mean something to you.
我人在现场  你没那么会演
I was there. You're not that good an actress.
我只是一时激情
I was just caught up in the moment.
就这么简单
That's all it was.
乔伊  抱歉让你难过
Joey, I'm sorry you feel bad, but...
你也曾跟别的女人上床
... haven't you slept with a woman
然后她比你更看重这段关系吧
and it meant more to her than to you?
没有
No.
-嗨  王八蛋  -萝伦  你好
- Hi, pig! - Hi, Lauren.
-萝伦  你好  -你好  王八蛋
- Hi, Lauren. - Hi pig.
抱歉吓到你了
Sorry I scared you in there.
没关系
It's okay.
对了...
By the way...
我只是在检查莲蓬头的按摩功能
... I was just checking the shower massager.
我有打去公司找你
I tried to reach you at work.
发生火灾了
There's been a fire.
什么  天哪
What? Oh, my God!
怎么了
What happened?
我们相信起火点在这里
We believe it originated here...
就是芳香室
...in the Aroma Room.
大家都逃出来了吗
Did everyone get out okay?
长颈鹿没事  海盗也是
The giraffe's okay, and so is the pirate.
-这是什么  -不要看  菲比
- What's this? - No, Pheebs, don't look!
你不会想看到下面的惨状的
You don't want to see what's under there!
领养的狗狗
The foster puppets!
其实没什么  就在这里  一直都在
It's not a big deal. It's right here, and it's all the time.
谢谢你这顿饭
Thanks again for lunch.
-我很愉快  -是吧
-This was pleasant. -lt was, wasn't it?
-那里的东西很好吃  -是吧
-The food there was great. -Wasn't it?
保重
So take care.
你也是
You too.
太好了  我再打给你  改天再聚
This is great, I'll give you a call. We should do it again!
太好了  我等你
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
-瑞秋  有消息吗  -在苏菲桌上
- Rachel. Any messages? - Sophie's desk.
-钱德勒  你会打给她吗  -当然不
- Chandler. Are you gonna call her? - No.
我很抱歉  好吗
I'm sorry, okay?
我软弱又可悲  抱歉
I'm weak and pathetic and sorry.
你去告诉她  现在就说
You are gonna tell her. You'll tell her now.
我不会打给你
I'm not gonna call you.
什么
What?
对不起
I'm sorry
对不起  我骗你说我会打给你
I'm sorry I said I was going to when I'm not.
跟你无关  真的
This has nothing to do with you. No.
也不是瑞秋的错  是我
And this isn't Rachel's fault. It's me.
我对女人有严重的心理障碍
I have serious problems when it comes to women.
我害怕承诺  害怕亲密
I have issues with commitment, intimacy...
害怕睫毛膏印子
... mascara goop.
真的很抱歉  但是...
I'm really sorry. It's just that...
我们不会在一起的
...this isn't going to work out.
我没料到会有这种结局
This isn't how I was hoping this would end...
但是我得谢谢你的诚实
... but I guess I have to appreciate your honesty.
太好了  我再打给你  改天再聚
This was great! I'll give you a call. We should do it again sometime!
无论如何  贝丝  我想说的是
Anyway, Beth, what I'm saying is...
那晚我跟你回家之前  应该先考虑你的心情
... I should have considered your feelings before I went home with you.
我最近有点体会到你的感觉
I've recently learned what it's like to be on your side...
我很抱歉
...and I'm sorry.
你可以原谅我吗
Do you think you can forgive me?
太好了  谢谢
Great. Thanks.
好的  再见
Ok, bye.
嗨  珍妮佛吗
Hello, Jennifer?
嗨  罗里欧太太  珍妮佛在吗
Hi, Mrs. Laurio. Is Jennifer there?
她不在是吧
She's not home, huh?
事实上  我应该也要找你
Actually I kind of need to talk to you too.